As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices We take in the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled
yeah yeah Here we are
in between the sea and
the sky Ready now for adventure We're itching
to try Get ready to roam So all aboard
now we're set to go Set sail to the ocean
so deep Ready for a truly grand adventure
Well don't you think that sounds really
fun All this excitement is second to none
As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices we take In the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled
If there's something that I just won't ever
forget It's the way that I felt when our
journey was set Now I won't be scared As
long as I keep that
feeling there With that,
let us keep up the pace While
enjoying every trip from place to
place Our timid hearts get the
rhythm ingrained So let's keep going,
adventure awaits So many treasures
await So now let's raise our voices
in pride Laughing out when they are
found With all the riches in hand,
everybody rejoices Party on,
cause we stand tall and proud
Life is adventurous, be aware it's
dangerous Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
This doesn't feel right,
leaving Perona behind.
We searched the whole island,
what else are we supposed to do?
It's just strange, where the
hell did she disappear to?
Okay, I think we're in the clear.
Drop the invisibility cloak.
A perfect escape.
We really cut it close.
I was sweating some invisible sweat there.
I'd still just like to know why.
Kuma the Tyrant appeared out
of the blue on Thriller Bark.
I can fill you in on that one. Well,
apparently Kuma was sent to inform Merde
of who'd been chosen to succeed Crocodile.
So there's a new warlord?
Yes, and he's quite the
controversial figure!
His names teach,
but he goes by Blackbeard From what
I hear, he's a nasty piece of work!
Take a look Second Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates, Firefist Ace,
now awaiting execution
at the prison Impel Down.
Ace is easily the most famous henchman
Whitebeard's got working under him.
A fine gift for teach to
present to the government.
True.
There's a feeling out
there that this could
spell very bad news for
our great pirate era.
The tides are turning towards a maelstrom.
There couldn't be a worse time
for Merde to be flat on his back.
I can see where you're
going with this, Doctor.
But I only care about one thing.
I want a nice wife. Sure.
Find me a corpse that
seems like your type.
I don't want a zombie!
I want a living woman filled
with blood and passion!
I can't believe everyone passed out in the
courtyard and slept through the whole day.
Are you surprised?
We did fight for a solid 24 hours.
I'm starving to death, Sanji!
We need some more cheese.
I need more than cheese. I'm a man.
I have to have meat.
Then help me bring my cooking
supplies over to the courtyard.
Our grateful group of survivors don't
want to budge an inch from that place,
so we'll just make the meal there.
Hope you don't mind.
We haven't felt the sun on our skin in
years, so we're trying to soak it up.
My men are so relieved,
they're weeping with joy.
How can you have this much energy?
It's weird. Really weird.
Are you certain that
you've got enough food?
We got back all the food
that was stolen from us.
On top of that, someone stocked
our stores with Mortius food.
I wonder who would do such a thing?
Well, whoever they are,
they've got a kind heart.
As if the food wasn't enough,
they left you all this, too.
You guys don't even have
to hunt for treasure!
It just delivers itself.
I'm in heaven.
This glass band is cool.
Yep, it looks slick.
I'm claiming this one.
What are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
Don't take that
Right, Nami?
Oh, he can have it.
That one is just costume jewelry.
That is not what I expected
you to say. But you?
You better not even think
of taking a single doubloon.
It would never even cross our minds
to steal from our saviors, Namizo.
Nice knife.
What did you just say?
Ah, nothing!
I'm sorry, I didn't notice
all the gemstones in it.
Huh?
It just kind of slipped out of my mouth.
Who's Namizo?
You know, this is a little strange.
I've got this feeling like you
and I have met somewhere before
Don't tell me you're Lola.
I am but I don't recall
telling you my name
Oh, what are you talking?
Whoa, hold on the Lola
like a fat big zombie Lola
I doubt this makes any sense to you,
so I'll explain later, but for now
Take this I want you to have it
what wait for me. Are you sure?
Help me give away some of our treasure!
I'm heading back in.
Is this everything you need me to take?
A storm must be coming!
Hey, storm.
Looks fine to me.
Oh, now this is bliss.
Come on, son.
Go on and give me everything you got.
I've never felt so alive.
I'm just happy we are.
Hey!
Huh?
Sure hope you guys are hungry!
It's Straw Hat!
Why didn't you ask us to carry that?
You guys have already done enough for us!
Is Zoro up yet?
No, he's fast asleep!
He's in the mansion!
Get your ass up! Chopper!
Got everything he asked
for bundled up here.
Oh, that's great, thanks!
How's Zoro doing?
I've never seen him in such
terrible condition before.
He was teetering on the edge of death.
It's bizarre.
Something happened while
we were passed out.
He was injured before, but not like this.
It is strange.
And it's even stranger that Kuma
the Tyrant would just up and leave.
And speaking of strange stuff,
why is Luffy so energetic?
Yeah, I don't get it either,
but it's fine with me.
You want to know what happened?
Then look no further!
We saw the whole thing from start
to finish, every damn detail,
and we can lay it out like you were there.
Come here.
What gives?
The guy saved your life, too.
You know?
Yeah, you were trying to take his place.
But he knocked you out shut up.
What did you two see just
hurry the hell up and tell
me what happened well
after I blacked out I mean,
I know the first part
That warlord's power was even
crazier than what you saw.
He laid his paws on Straw Hat and
made this bubble come out of him.
He said he'd extracted all
the damage done to his body.
Wait, he did what?
So he took that big ball
of suffering, and then...
Just the tiniest bit of that stuff had the
swords been screaming like
he was being murdered?
But that didn't stop him from taking on
every ounce of that big ball of pain!
It moved me to tears man
yeah same here i was bawling!
I see that explains why luffy's just fine
and zoro's damn near
comatose reckless moron?
What happened here?
Nothing at all.
Well, come on.
Now that you know, let's go spread
the tale of how brave your friend is.
Damn straight.
Everybody's got to hear this.
Hold it.
You're keeping your mouth shut.
Zoro didn't do this for Luffy's gratitude.
And besides,
how do you think it
would make Luffy feel if
he found out Zoro is
suffering from his pain?
Don't say a word or I'll
kick the crap out of you
Everyone's still alive, right?
That's all that matters.
Now, let's go eat!
Huh?
Holy crap.
These Straw Hat guys are so cool.
With a crew like that, their
captain is one lucky dude.
And now I know?
Hey you two, where'd you go?
Didn't you guys say you had
something you wanted to tell us?
So what happened?
Why does it mean so much to you?
Everyone's still alive.
That's all that matters.
Man, I'm gonna tell them so bad! Right?
How we supposed to sit
on such an amazing story?
Uh, what the heck?
Let's get it!
Man, this is the most delicious
thing I've ever tasted!
It's been years, entire years
since we've had a proper meal!
I'm so damn happy to be alive!
There's plenty for everyone,
so don't hold back.
to indulge in such delicacies again why my
taste buds are leaping they're dancing in
unrestrained joy oh my but i don't have
taste buds do i just shut up and eat already
honestly though i uh excuse
me getting to gorge myself on
such mouth-watering meals two
days in I'm starting to worry.
I've gained some weight.
You're nothing but bones.
Now shut your damn charge.
That's the funny skeleton I've ever seen.
How can you move without any muscles?
Who cares? He's great.
Dinner.
Yeah. Dinner. Come on.
Dinner. Oh, baby. Dinner.
Shaking for dinner.
Super.
They haven't even opened up the booth yet,
and everyone's already lost their mind.
It's as loud as a battlefield in here,
and he's sleeping right through it.
That's about normal.
Hey, Chopper, here!
Luffy!
It's Zorro's portion.
Now drink up. Back off!
It's gonna help him.
Zoro loves booze.
It's gonna make him feel better.
He needs medicine, not booze!
How about meat?
That's like a medicine.
No, not quite.
Your concern will just
have to be enough, okay?
You're concerned, and that's it.
I didn't even notice there
was a piano in this room.
Hey, what's this?
I thought you said you were
a violinist or something.
I am, but I can play just
about any instrument.
That's so.
You're pretty talented.
Um, you mind talking about
what happened out there?
You had another witness,
and I saw the whole thing.
i was quite touched by the two of you by
your bravery and your
compassion friendship is
a beautiful thing you shouldn't put me in
the same boat with zoro
i just end up looking
stupid in comparison
no you had just as much
resolve as he did there
a song you'd like to
hear anything at all
i gladly take requests
huh anything i can think
of well in that case
I thought you said you
were taking requests,
you jerk I thought that
was Binx's brew Oh,
it's been ages since I last heard
this song Such a nostalgic feeling
Good pick, Brooke.
I always loved this song.
Of course it's a classic.
All the pirates used to sing
it back in the good old days.
It was sung in times of sorrow and joy.
So what do you think?
You're gonna join my crew?
We could use a musician, huh?
Come on.
You got your shadow back.
You can sail anywhere
with us now, day or night.
It's not that easy for me.
Although I'd like to.
There's something important
I haven't told you yet.
What's that?
I have to keep my word.
I made a promise to a friend.
It's still my life's goal
to fulfill that promise.
And if I don't, I wouldn't have
the right to call myself a man.
Oh, you're talking about Laboon, right?
I know about that.
Franky and the guys told me
the whole story is that so I
don't know how much they told
you exactly but he's a whale
you see there's a cape that's
what I'm trying to say we've
been to the twin caves and
we've met Laboon it's the truth
I swear it and I can tell you
this for a fact too the boon
has been right there for 50
years waiting for his friends to
return.
Hey, something wrong, Skeleton?
Why's the tempo slowing down?
So you can imagine how surprised I was.
It's pretty crazy you turned out to be
one of the That frenzy's been waiting for.
Kind of feels like fate, huh?
And that promise you made, he still
remembers it just as clear as you do.
Laboon's gonna be so happy
when he finds out you're okay.
Please, just give me a moment here.
You...
I can't believe this.
So what you're saying is you
guys met Laboon you truly did?
Yep, even after 50 years all this time.
Laboon's still waiting at
the Cape for me to come back,
just as we left him, you're not joking?
Nope.
We can back him up on that, your
big buddy's there, all right?
Yep, and he's doing well.
Yeah, he's doing great.
He's as big as a damn mountain.
That's incredible.
The last time I saw him, he
was the size of a small boat.
He was so adorable.
He could be difficult at
times, but oh, he loved music.
He was such a good boy.
Even now, I remember
exactly what he looked like.
I can picture him when we said goodbye.
This is wonderful.
Even after all this time,
he's still doing okay.
I've never been this
happy in my entire life.
What's up with this little whale?
He won't stop following our ship.
Probably got separated
from his family. Poor guy.
Lost in this big ocean.
You look so sad little guy.
You're just a baby aren't you?
Hey captain Yorkie, how about we
cheer up the little guy with a song?
That's a brilliant idea Brooke.
All right everybody grab your instrument
The rumbar pirates can bring a
smile to the face of any creature.
Let's show them how we do it boys
Rise and shine, my fellow pirates!
The day is upon us, and it is gorgeous.
We'll start this day with a song.
Now, let me see what shall
be this week's power tune.
Ah, yes, the Black
Handkerchief of Happiness.
Don't be afraid to sing along, everyone!
It's a white handkerchief.
Careful now, he's on the ground.
Run away, precious white.
Handkerchief, you cannot escape your bait.
It is far too late,
the octopus won't wait!
Cut it out, Brooke, it's
too damn early for that!
We're awake, we're
awake, just please stop.
Mercy man, please?
Run away, find the right,
handkerchief of happiness.
Hey, Brooke, think you could do
a ballad version of Binks's brew?
Of course, Captain's Choice coming up.
It's the whale, the
same one from yesterday.
You're still with us.
You should be out there.
Looking for your pod.
Oh, he's so cute.
Hey, how long do you think
he's gonna follow us?
I don't know.
His poor mom's got to
be worried about him.
Here, have some food, Laboon.
Laboon, huh?
Since when did you give
the big boy a name?
Enemy attack!
Ow!
Are you two all right?
You've got to hurry up
and help us back on board.
His legs hurt pretty bad.
Captain York, two men overboard.
Then throw them a raft.
We're kind of busy saving the ship.
I suppose that's the best I
can do, since I can't swim.
Mom, Laboon, you saved us.
Hey, we're okay, guys.
Good job, boy.
All right, everyone, time to sing.
You know the tune?
The boon aren't you freezing?
Come on, men!
Let's protect Laboon! Yeah!
Nobody messes with our
buddy and gets away with it!
You are a good boy, aren't you?
He's really grown quite attached
to you, hasn't he, Brooke?
You got that right.
That's because he loves music so much.
Nah, I betcha it's just cause your
head is the same shape as his.
So, do you think you can do something?
We've all tried talking to
him, but it's just no good.
I'm afraid he won't listen to us.
Do you understand?
There's simply no way that we can keep on
protecting him like
this where we're going.
The fact is, he's still a child.
We can't take him with
us to the Grand Line.
I need you to listen to me, Laboon.
No, wait, we'll sing later, all right?
We really need to talk first.
Look, there's no denying that you and I
are friends, but you are still a whale.
The Couran line is too dangerous
for a young child like you.
It might be different
if you were fully grown,
but there are enormous beasts in that sea?
more savage than any in the West Blue.
Baboon, please believe me.
I tried, but he refuses to listen to me.
Maybe we should just sing then.
You know the song I mean.
That might make it worse.
Captain.
I know it's tough,
but we have to ignore him no matter what,
so don't look back until he swims away.
Remember, we're doing
this for his own good.
This wind's gonna capsize us! What now?
Look!
Right over there!
You see, men?
What did I tell you?
That's the entrance to the Grand Line!
Oh, we really made it at long last.
We made it, sir!
I don't think anyone's got
sight of him for a week now!
I know it was a cruel thing to
do, but it was for his own good.
Let's just hope that he's able to
reunite with his family someday.
This is it, men!
Is everyone ready to do this?
I am I!
We are more ready!
And let's go!
Onward to conquer the
world's greatest sea! Yeah!
I'm the lighthouse keeper here.
The name's Crocus.
I'm impressed you guys got
over reverse mountain alive.
Welcome to the pirates graveyard.
Hey, give us a break, old man.
We're not dead yet, are we?
I'm Calico Yorkie, captain
of the Rumbar Pirates.
You might have heard of our
exploits in the West Blue.
We earned ourselves quite the
reputation around those parts.
Sorry to drop in on you like this,
but our ship took a hell of a beating.
You can drop anchor here
as long as you need,
but you gotta pay me for the
space with food and booze.
Is that how it is?
You extort from pirates, huh?
Fine by me.
Hey, you should celebrate with us.
because we're going to have one hell
of a party tonight, aren't we, boys?
So is that way that followed you guys
down some kind of pet or something?
Huh?
The moon!
How did... Ah!
Broke, I live!
All right, Brooke, I think it's
about time to play the song.
You really like that song, huh, Captain?
You're damn right.
It's the Pirate's Anthem.
Hey, the bone, you like
it too, don't you, boy?
Gather up along the crew Inside your ship,
our faces Seen and hoops
to where Who knows,
the waves will be our guide Or across
the ocean's hide Praise the sunshine,
poor and white Mercy's
out to you Hey, Brocus,
have any requests You would like to hear?
You really can play anything, Hatch and
Broke All right, pirates, sing it loud!
I hope you can understand, but
you can't follow us this time.
The Grand Line is too treacherous for you.
Why don't you stay put and wait
for us here for a while, Laboon?
Our plan is to sail our ship
straight across this sea.
Once we've sailed through the Grand Line,
our ship will have made a
circle around the entire world.
And that means we'll be crossing the
Red Line again, just like we are now.
We'll come back to this
cape as fast as we can.
We'll just wait and see.
It'll only be maybe two
or three years tops.
If you can wait that long,
you'll see all of us again.
And by the time we make it back here,
you'll have grown big and strong
enough to travel along with us!
See you later, Laboon!
You take care of yourself, pal!
Laboon!
This will be the last time we say goodbye.
I promise we're coming back.
We're your friends.
Nothing will ever change that.
Hey, Laboon!
Don't go swimming off now.
Once we travel the world,
we're coming right back here.
Just wait for us.
Hey, Brooke, you're really amazing
with that sword. What do you say?
Think you can teach me a few tricks?
What is it? A tornado?
How?
It was sunny a second ago.
What happened to run away?
The place was cursed.
I've been trying to tell you guys.
This is a disaster.
These seas are a complete nightmare.
I just can't keep up.
You know what I Always say
bitter seas make for sweet boos.
At the end of the day, Brooke
you want to play a number for us?
Can't beat good tunes and beer.
You know the song.
I was starting to think you'd never ask.
All right, here I go.
Of course, it's a mirror.
I keep forgetting.
I'm a skeleton now Ow,
captain, stop it, let me down,
why are you punishing me too?
Because I don't want you two
fighting over every little thing.
It's not some little thing, this lunatic
almost hit me with a stray bullet,
I could have died.
Yeah, well you didn't, okay,
and he said he was sorry, what's done is
done, no point in going on about it now.
That hurt, good, it proves you're alive.
Alright, fair enough.
Look at the stars, a sea of
lights spreading out forever,
I wonder if Laboon is
looking up at the same stars.
What do you think, Captain?
Hey guys, come look, Brooke's
getting emotional out here.
I was being sincere, don't make fun of me.
It's the marines, what do we do?
Same thing we always do, give them hell.
Damn, look at that, Captain, Yorkie's
bounty went up again, he's on a roll.
Eat that, let's celebrate with a song,
Yorkie, Yorkie, a bounty on his head.
Out the twin cape flies the
news, the navy wants his head.
Bad news, men!
There's something wrong with the captain.
He ain't looking so good.
I'm serious! Huh?
A virus?
I'm afraid so.
Everyone stay out.
We've got a dozen men infected already.
I figure they must have contracted it
when we passed through that jungle.
I've never seen anything like it.
None of my treatments work.
We've all got to be careful now.
If this plague keeps spreading, we
won't have enough men to sail this ship.
Please hang in there, Captain.
Come on, don't sound so depressed.
We're the Rumbar Pirates, remember?
We bring smiles to children's faces.
Though I admit I've seen better days, and
that goes for the rest of the ship, too.
I'm sorry I won't be able to
travel the Grand Line with you.
We'll have to part ways here.
I'll take this ship, but I want all
of you to move forward with a new one.
Captain, no.
We can't risk the infection spreading
any more than it already has.
We'll drop you off.
Try passing through the Calm Belt and
look for help for the sick crew members.
It'll all work out somehow, I hope.
I'm sorry, guys.
Give Laboon my regards.
Wipe those tears away.
Stand up straight. Yes.
Brooke?
Yes.
Give them hope.
I will, my captain!
I swear, as long as I live!
I will never forget those words.
Hey, hear that?
I've engraved them in my heart.
Captain, we'll meet again!
So take care.
We may be parting ways now?
But this isn't the end!
So please don't die.
Take off that mask.
Let me see your face.
We'll all sing together again someday.
Hey Brooke.
While you're here.
Why don't you send me off
With my favorite song?
Gather up all of the crew.
It's time to ship out Binx's brew.
Sea wind blows to where?
Who knows the waves will be our guide?
Or across the ocean's tide?